[{"answer": "0pm", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 9, "question": "", "qSentId": 8},{"answer": " I think I might get a snack in a little bit.  Im hungry", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 12, "question": "0pm", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Didnt you eat dinner", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 13, "question": " I think I might get a snack in a little bit.  Im hungry", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I did, but I didnt really have time to cook a big meal.  I just had a sandwich.  Ar", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Didnt you eat dinner", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Not me.  Im stuffed", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I did, but I didnt really have time to cook a big meal.  I just had a sandwich.  Ar", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " How come?  Did you cook a big meal", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Not me.  Im stuffed", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " No, I never cook", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " How come?  Did you cook a big meal", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Does your roommate cook with the groceries you buy", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 21, "question": " No, I never cook", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Nope, he doesnt cook either", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Does your roommate cook with the groceries you buy", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Well then, how do you eat", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Nope, he doesnt cook either", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " We go to the dining halls on campus", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well then, how do you eat", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Oh, really?  Ive never been to those.  I never lived on campus", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 28, "question": " We go to the dining halls on campus", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Theyre really great", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Oh, really?  Ive never been to those.  I never lived on campus", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Can anyone go", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Theyre really great", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " No.  You have to buy a meal plan in order to eat there", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Can anyone go", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " How much does that cost", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 32, "question": " No.  You have to buy a meal plan in order to eat there", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " It costs $1500 per semester", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 33, "question": " How much does that cost", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Whoa!  That sounds like a lot.  Wouldnt it be cheaper to eat at home", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 34, "question": " It costs $1500 per semester", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I dont think so.  With the meal plan, I can eat in any dining hall, as much food a", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Whoa!  That sounds like a lot.  Wouldnt it be cheaper to eat at home", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I guess thats pretty reasonable then", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I dont think so.  With the meal plan, I can eat in any dining hall, as much food a", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " I think so.  Plus, its really convenient, and it saves me time.  I dont have to coo", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " I guess thats pretty reasonable then", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I must admit, I do get tired of grocery shopping and cooking.  I never have th", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I think so.  Plus, its really convenient, and it saves me time.  I dont have to coo", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Yeah, with school I dont know how I would do it", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 49, "question": " I must admit, I do get tired of grocery shopping and cooking.  I never have th", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Dont you miss eating what you like though", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Yeah, with school I dont know how I would do it", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Dont you miss eating what you like though", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I mean, dont you just get served whatever the dining hall made that day", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " No, no.  Theres tons of food to choose from.  They have sandwiches, a variet", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " I mean, dont you just get served whatever the dining hall made that day", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 57, "question": " No, no.  Theres tons of food to choose from.  They have sandwiches, a variet", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yep.  Tonight I had chicken noodle soup, a salad, pasta with chicken, and a slic", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " That sounds a lot better than my measly sandwich.  No wonder youre full", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Yep.  Tonight I had chicken noodle soup, a salad, pasta with chicken, and a slic", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " It was really good", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": " That sounds a lot better than my measly sandwich.  No wonder youre full", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Maybe Ill get on the meal plan next term.  It sounds pretty good", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 67, "question": " It was really good", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Id recommend it", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Maybe Ill get on the meal plan next term.  It sounds pretty good", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " How do I get it", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Id recommend it", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " You can buy it online or go by the Food Services department on campus.  The", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 70, "question": " How do I get it", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Im definitely going to consider it", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 74, "question": " You can buy it online or go by the Food Services department on campus.  The", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Do you want to go get that snack before we start studying", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Im definitely going to consider it", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Yeah.  Ill be right back", "docId": "05-10", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Do you want to go get that snack before we start studying", "qSentId": 75}]
